ozonemedia.com 2014-09-20

# Ozone Media | Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

#### 

Ozone Media Pvt Ltd (“Ozone Media”) is the Definitive South Asian Audience Platform enabling advertisers and marketers across the region to communicate with their audiences and helping publishers to grow their revenues with better optimization and campaign planning. We have developed the application Adadyn, which helps advertisers create personalized ads for every single customer dynamically at run time. With a unique rule based engine, it allows for a much more deeper and meaningful engagement with the customers. We are headquartered in India, with an office in Bangalore and an international office in New Jersey, USA. We provide this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) so that we may inform you about how our ad optimization technology, including our Ad Network Platform for online advertisers, including Real-Time Bidding Service and Adadyn (collectively, the “Service”) gathers and processes information on behalf of (i) advertisers, agencies and ad networks, and any other media-buying clients (collectively “Demand Partners”); and (ii) website owners, mobile application owners, ad networks, ad exchanges, sell-side platforms and any other suppliers of advertising inventory for sale (collectively “Supply Partners”); wherein Demand Partners and Supply Partners in (i) and (ii) above together are “Clients”. This policy also outlines our privacy practices on our corporate Website (“Website”), [www.ozonemedia.com.]()

Ozone Media recognizes and values your privacy and we are committed to protecting the confidentiality of your personal information. In order to better protect you, we have adopted a strong privacy policy that allows you to monitor the information you have provided us. We will seek your consent before collecting any information about you, and you will always be aware of exactly what we are going to use the information for. If at any time you wish to withdraw your personal information, all you are required to do is to contact us at [privacy@ozonemedia.com](mailto:privacy@ozonemedia.com) and tell us exactly what information you would like removed. 

You will find an explanation of our Privacy Policy below; to give you a better understanding of the lengths we would go to protect you. 

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, so please visit ozonemedia.com regularly to review our privacy statement. 

##### USAGE

We use cookies and web beacons for select purposes. We use them in order to track when we deliver an advertising impression so that we can correctly credit it to a Demand Partner and invoice that Demand Partner. We also drop a cookie for counting frequency of exposure to a particular ad to meet a Demand Partner’s campaign objective around frequency capping. As a buyer of RTB inventory available for sale on sell-side platforms and exchanges (Supply Partner), we do map anonymized user identification number (“UID”) against Supply Partner’s anonymized UID so as to gain handle to the underlying impression and be able to serve appropriate ad on that impression.

##### PERSONAL INFORMATION

The following information about you will be considered as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy-

  * Email address
  * Credit card information
  * Your name
  * Phone number
  * Residential Address
  * Any other information collected from you

We do not sell, trade, permit usage or rent your personal information to any third party unless we have been expressly authorized by you either in writing or electronically to do so. We may at times provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third parties, however this information when disclosed will be in an aggregate form and does not contain any of your personally identifiable information. We conduct internal audits to ensure that we are complying with the policies in place to protect you.

We may disclose your personal information solely in the legitimate conduct of business to deliver services and to provide special offers designed to meet your demands. We may also release information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (1) comply with legal or regulatory requirements; (2) enforce or apply terms of the our Web site user agreement; or (3) protect our rights, property or safety of the rights of others. 

We expressly forbid our clients from sending us any of your personal information. To the best of our ability, we have taken all the precautions possible to avoid receiving personal information from our clients. If, despite these measures, we do receive some personal information from a client, we shall take all measures to remove such personal information from our servers and records.

##### COOKIES

“Cookies” are strings of text that a web site transmits to a user’s computer. Cookies enable a website to keep track of a user’s preferences and activities relating to that website. Our website creates a temporary cookie for each visit in order to facilitate the visit. These cookies automatically expire as soon as you leave our website. If you do not wish to receive these cookies, you may set your browser to reject the cookies, although doing so may affect your ability to perform certain transactions on our website. 

The main purpose of using these cookies is to improve your experience. For example, our cookies allow you to login without repeatedly typing the registered email address or registration number and password. We also use them to deliver information and fresh content specific to your interests. Cookies are widely used on most major sites. Cookies can also be used to track a user’s browsing or online purchasing habits and to target advertisements to specific users.

We may use third party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. In particular, refer to the

  * The [appnexus privacy policy](http://appnexus.com/platform-policyappnexus%20privacy%20policy) and [cookie opt out instructions](http://appnexus.com/platform-policy#choices').
  * [The Google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and opt out option on [this page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?sig=ACi0TCiwPt9SUVQND8YGFVWPN7cfRJr613NqcLLSpCO68dEkwNAl_s4PKa-JnIZt2WvtEV_W_8AaHpj1BQ9DtWPZNcG_u8sZZxrbvZPpq6tmMEUJ4XMPS5WwVasuk-_cO9u6VFs6aS3QkjH1Lqs282rIlfh0sDydM5de_mmFceOjKP0Xf8rakE_QtxVkC8czc5NeFCdnaOQv&hl=e).

To opt out of Ozone Media products' cookies, please click visit our privacy policies of our products.

The World Privacy Forum has published an article on cookie opt-out. If you would like to read more about this, please visit this link: <http://www.worldprivacyforum.org/cookieoptout.html>. You may follow the procedure laid out in the said website to opt out of Cookie.

##### OUR SECURITY & STORAGE PROCEDURES FOR YOUR DATA

At Ozone Media we make protection of your personal information from loss, theft or misuse our top priority. All information we have collected is stored using the same security measures that we use to protect our own proprietary corporate data. Only authorized users are able to access the data we collect and store.

At times we may collect Non-Personal Information (NPI) via our service, including but not limited to your IP host address, the date, time, and time zone of the ad request, pages viewed, browser type, the referring URL, and your computer’s operating system. We retain this NPI at a user level for a certain period in order to ensure that our service is functioning properly. We may also retain data at an aggregated level, so that no individual user, albeit anonymous, could be picked out from the data, indefinitely for purposes of reporting and system analytics. 

##### INFORMATION SHARING

Unless otherwise permitted by you, we will not share even your NPI to third parties. However, we might be under an obligation to share this information with the following third-parties and in the following circumstances: (i) to the appropriate authorities when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, or in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person; (ii) to a court of law, arbitration panel, or similar body to enforce or protect our rights either under law or as granted by an agreement; (iii) to the company or entity that acquires all or substantially all of our assets, including if the acquisition occurs as the result of our bankruptcy; or (iv) to third parties that help us provide the Service to Clients, or that enter into strategic partnerships with the company which allow us to expand the Service for our Clients.

##### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY & PARENTAL CONSENT

This website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information from children. Please be aware that we have not designed this website for, and do not intend it to be used by anyone under the age of 18. We specifically request that persons under the age of 18 do not use this website or submit or post information to the website. Should we inadvertently acquire personal information or other data from users under the age of 18, we will not knowingly provide this data to any third party for any purpose whatsoever, and any subsequent disclosure would be due to the fact the user under age 18 used our website and submitted personal information without solicitation by or permission from us.

##### OTHER SITES

Ozone Media is only responsible for the privacy statement and content of this website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the use of cookies on websites that you may have accessed from this site.

##### CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY 

In the future, we may need to change this privacy policy. All changes will be made here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. This statement was last updated on 1st November, 2011.

##### GOVERNING LAW

This is an Indian website and is subject to the laws of India. Ozone Media may have to disclose personally identifiable information without your permission when required by law, or in good faith belief that such action is necessary to investigate or protect against harmful activities to our clients. Please note, laws related to personally identifiable information vary from country to country.

##### NO UNLAWFUL OR PROHIBITED USE

As a condition of your use of this website, you agree that you will not use this website or the information or software contained herein for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these terms and conditions.

##### YOUR CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

By submitting your information, you consent to the use of that information as set out in this Privacy Policy. We welcome your views on this website and the Privacy Policy. If you have questions or comments about our administration of your personal information, please contact us at [privacy@ozonemedia.com](mailto:privacy@ozonemedia.com). You may also use this address to communicate any concerns you may have regarding compliance with this Privacy Policy. 

##### DISCLAIMER

While every effort is made to ensure the accuracy of information offered on these pages, we shall have no liability for errors, omissions or inadequacies in the information contained herein or for interpretations thereof. This website could include inaccuracies or out-dated information and is subject to change at any time without notice. Your use of this website is at your own risk. You agree to hold Ozone Media harmless from and not sue Ozone Media for any claims based upon using this website.

THE INFORMATION, DOCUMENTATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES CONTAINED ON THE OZONE MEDIA WEBSITE ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. OZONE MEDIA AND ITS SUPPLIERS DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES RELATING TO THE INFORMATION, DOCUMENTATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES CONTAINED ON THE OZONE MEDIA WEBSITE, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY WARRANTIES AGAINST INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS, MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. SOME STATES OR JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR LIMITATIONS ON HOW LONG AN IMPLIED WARRANTY MAY LAST, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, TO THE EXTENT INAPPLICABLE. OZONE MEDIA SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DAMAGES, WHETHER DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL, AS A RESULT OF THE REPRODUCTION, MODIFICATION, DISTRIBUTION OR USE OF THE INFORMATION, DOCUMENTATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES.
